<!--RSS.XML -->
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>NASA Breaking News</title><link>http://www.nasa.gov/audience/formedia/features/index.html</link><description>A RSS news feed containing the latest NASA news articles and press releases.</description><language>en-us</language><docs>http://blogs.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><managingEditor>jim.wilson@nasa.gov</managingEditor><webMaster>brian.dunbar@nasa.gov</webMaster><item><title>NASA Mission Helps Craft 3-D Image Of Buried Mars Flood Channels</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_13-070_MRO_3D_Flood_Channels.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_13-070_MRO_3D_Flood_Channels.html</guid> <description>NASA's Mars Reconnaissance Orbiter (MRO) has provided images allowing scientists for the first time to create a 3-D reconstruction of ancient water channels below the Martian surface.</description> <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item> <item><title>NASA TV Briefing Discusses Curiosity Rover Analysis of Mars Rock</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-045_Curiosity_Mars_Rock.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-045_Curiosity_Mars_Rock.html</guid> <description>NASA will hold a news conference at 1 p.m. EDT, Tuesday, March 12, to discuss the Curiosity rover's analysis of the first sample of rock powder ever collected on Mars.</description> <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item> <item><title>NASA Briefing Highlights Expedition 36-37 Space Station Crew</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-043_EXP_36_37_News_briefing.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-043_EXP_36_37_News_briefing.html</guid> <description>NASA's Johnson Space Center in Houston will host a crew news conference at 1 p.m. CDT (2 p.m. EDT) Tuesday, March 19, to preview the May launch of an American, an Italian and a Russian to the International Space Station.</description> <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item> <item><title>NASA, Lockheed Martin Announce Exploration Design Challenge for Students</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-044_Exploration_Design_Challenge.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-044_Exploration_Design_Challenge.html</guid> <description>NASA and Lockheed Martin Corp. of Bethesda, Md., will involve students in the flight test of NASA's Orion spacecraft through an Exploration Design Challenge to be unveiled in Houston on Monday, March 11.</description> <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item> <item><title>NASA TV Coverage Planned For Space Station Soyuz Landing</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-042_Soyuz_Landing_Coverage.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-042_Soyuz_Landing_Coverage.html</guid> <description>NASA Television will provide live coverage March 13-15 as three crew members aboard the International Space Station end almost five months at the orbiting laboratory.</description> <pubDate>Thu, 07 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item> <item><title>NASA Selects Contractors for Engineering Solutions and Prototyping at Marshall Space Flight Center</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_C13-013_MSFC_Eng_Prototyping.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_C13-013_MSFC_Eng_Prototyping.html</guid> <description>NASA has selected three companies to provide engineering solutions and products to Marshall Space Flight Center in Huntsville, Ala.</description> <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item> <item><title>NASA Selects Education Support Contractor</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_C13-012_GRC_Educ_Support.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_C13-012_GRC_Educ_Support.html</guid> <description>NASA has selected Paragon Tec Inc. of Cleveland to support educational programs at the agency's Glenn Research Center in Cleveland, NASA Headquarters in Washington, and other NASA centers, as necessary.</description> <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item> <item><title>NASA Selects Safety, Health, Environmental and Mission Assurance Services Contract</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_C13-014_GRC_Health_Safety.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_C13-014_GRC_Health_Safety.html</guid> <description>NASA has selected Science Applications International Corporation (SAIC) of McLean, Va., to provide safety, health, environmental and mission assurance services at the agency's Glenn Research Center in Cleveland and Plum Brook Station in Sandusky, Ohio.</description> <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item> <item><title>NASA Transfers Operational Control of Environmental Satellite</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_13-068_Suomi_NPP.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_13-068_Suomi_NPP.html</guid> <description>The Suomi National Polar-orbiting Partnership (NPP) satellite, a partnership between NASA and the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA), was transitioned to NOAA operational organization control Feb. 22. The transition marks the next step of the mission that supports NASA's Earth science research and NOAA's weather forecasting missions.</description> <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item> <item><title>California Students Speak Live With Space Station Astronauts</title> <link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-039_California_ISS_downlink.html</link> <guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2013/mar/HQ_M13-039_California_ISS_downlink.html</guid> <description>Students in California will speak with Expedition 34 astronauts aboard the International Space Station Tuesday, March 5, at Monrovia High School near Los Angeles. News media representatives are invited to attend.</description> <pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2013 00:00:00 EST</pubDate> </item></channel></rss>
